<archimate:BusinessObject
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Shared Governance Framework"
    id="id-a8c96ad771424a80a19f6d9ef5b5c0b9"
    documentation="DESCRIPTION:&#xD;&#xA;A shared governance framework is formed by [re]usable governance resources, with  convergence power, in relation to public policy goals attainment, given by their functioning impact via communication and harmonization, across the levels of a public administration (central, regional, local) towards the achievement of the public policy goals, enabling :&#xD;&#xA;i)&#x9;structural interoperability by organisational resources supporting reusing and/or sharing of digital public services (i.e. public services catalogue enabling provisioning/consuming public services cross public administrations and cross borders);&#xD;&#xA;ii)&#x9;behavioural interoperability by organisational resources supporting exchanging capabilities of data, information or knowledge with internal/external peers (i.e. service delivery model enabling that data/information/knowledge be provisioned/consumed cross public administrations and cross borders); and&#xD;&#xA;iii)&#x9;governance interoperability by governance resources supporting the collaboration with internal/external peers exchanging data, information or knowledge (i.e. Organisational Interoperability Agreements on organisational terms/conditions enabling sharing, reuse and exchange of data/information/knowledge cross public administrations and cross borders).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;INTEROPERABILITY SALIENCY&#xD;&#xA;IoP dimensions: Structural IoP, Behavioral IoP, Governance IoP&#xD;&#xA;This ABB is a key interoperability enabler because it supports to achieve legal interoperability with public policy goals convergence value by  all in all enabling i) sharing/provisioning/reusing/consumption of legislation on digital public services,  ii) the exchange of data, information, and knowledge between digital public services, and iii) collaboration between digital public services">
  <properties
      key="ID"
      value="ABB358"/>
  <properties
      key="dct:type"
      value="eira:SharedGovernanceFramework"/>
  <properties
      key="dct:publisher"/>
  <properties
      key="dct:modified"/>
  <properties
      key="dct:description"/>
  <properties
      key="eira:view"
      value="Organisational view"/>
</archimate:BusinessObject>
